# KARMASAKSHI GOYAL

+91 97399 31869

karmasakshi121@gmail.com

karmasakshi.com

Mumbai

## **PROFILE**

Full-stack web developer with over 6 years of professional experience in architecting, designing and building web applications.

Technical leader with over 5 years of professional experience in piloting, steering and expanding development teams.

Developability and usability enthusiast.

# **SKILLS**

CSS Frameworks: Bootstrap, Foundation, Spectre

Databases: MongoDB, MySQL, Redis

JavaScript Back-End Frameworks (Node.js): Apollo Server, Express, Sails

JavaScript Front-End Frameworks: Angular, Angular Material, AngularJS, Apollo Client,

Clarity Design System, jQuery, React PHP Frameworks: CodeIgniter, Laravel

Other Libraries: amCharts, amMaps, Bootstrap, Foundation, RxJS, SocketIO

PaaS: Amazon Web Services, Firebase Preprocessors: LESS, SASS, TypeScript

Software and SaaS: BitBucket, Git, GitHub, Google Analytics, Google Maps, JIRA,

Mixpanel

## **PROJECTS**

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

- 1. INTELLECT DESIGN ARENA LTD., Mumbai, August 2016 January 2019 (2 years 6 months)
  - a. Contextual Banking Experience (CBX): A corporate banking platform for banks around the world.
    - Front-End Module Lead, Cash-Flow Forecasting September 2018 - January 2019 (5 months)
    - Front-End Module Lead, Balance and Transaction Reporting March 2018 - August 2018 (6 months)
    - Front-End Team Lead
       August 2016 February 2018 (1 year 7 months)

amCharts, amMaps, Angular, Apollo Client, Clarity Design System, SASS

- 2. FIRST NOTIFY SERVICES PVT. LTD., Mumbai, September 2015 April 2016 (8 months)
  - a. **Grabslot**: A marketplace of guaranteed online ad inventories.
    - Senior Full-Stack Developer
       November 2015 April 2016 (6 months) Angular, Angular Material, MongoDB, Redis,
       Sails
  - b. **WarCircle**: A debating platform, now with over 5000 visits every week.
    - Senior Full-Stack Developer
       September 2015 October 2015 (2 months) Laravel, React
- 3. SPORTKIX PTY. LTD., Mumbai, October 2014 September 2015 (11 months)
  - a. **Sportkix**: A worldwide sports news portal covering over 20 sports.
    - JavaScript Developer
       October 2014 September 2015 (11 months) AngularJS, Foundation, SocketIO
- 4. DONE SOLUTIONS PVT. LTD. & VIVACONNECT PVT. LTD., Mumbai, September 2013 October 2014 (1 year 1 month)
  - a. **Done**: An online ordering platform for over 15 restaurants, some serving over 5 cities.
    - Software Developer
       December 2013 October 2014 (10 months) AngularJS, Express, LESS, MongoDB
  - b. **MDConnect**: A platform for doctors to interact with their patients.
    - Software Developer
       September 2013 November 2013 (3 months) MySQL, PHP
- 5. MN&C SUPPLY LINKS RETAIL INDIA PVT. LTD., Mumbai, December 2012 May 2013 (6 months)
  - a. LocalBanya: A grocery delivery service serving Mumbai and Pune, with over 150 orders every day.
    - Intern
       December 2012 May 2013 (6 months) CodeIgniter, jQuery, MySQL

### **FREELANCE**

1. **Transportex**: A portal simplifying employee travel.

November 2016 - December 2016 (2 months)

Google Maps, MongoDB, Redis, Sails

2. **Ediffy Attendance**: A portal for managing attendance in classrooms.

June 2016 - October 2016 (5 months)

AngularJS, MySQL, Sails

3. Crumbroll: A list discovery platform.

November 2015 - August 2016 (10 months)

AngularJS, Bootstrap, jQuery

4. **Frapp**: A student-only platform for discounts, internships and more.

February 2015 - July 2015 (6 months)

AngularJS, MongoDB, Sails

Other projects of shorter durations have been excluded.

#### **SELF**

1. Cinepotato: A serverless movie discovery website.

August 2018 - Present (4 months)

Angular, Firebase

2. 200mins: A movie discovery website.

April 2016 - July 2016 (4 months)

AngularJS, MongoDB, Sails

3. **Bevereq**: A socket-based beverage request management website.

December 2014 - January 2015 (2 months)

AngularJS, Sails, SocketIO

Other projects of shorter durations have been excluded.

## **AWARDS**

1. Special Recognition Award, Hackadrone 2018, Hyderabad

February 2018

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

1. MongoDB Certified Developer, Associate Level

April 2015

Certificate no.: 776-411-905

#### **EDUCATION**

1. Master of Computer Application (M.C.A.), Manipal University, Manipal

2010 - 2013 (3 years)

7.23/10

2. Bachelor of Commerce (B·Com.), Mumbai University, Mumbai

2007 - 2010 (3 years)

62.29%

3. **XIIth**, Smt. Lilavatibai Podar Senior Secondary School, I.S.C., Mumbai 2007

67.67%

4. **Xth**, Smt. Lilavatibai Podar High School, I.C.S.E., Mumbai

2005

86.17%